You know, watching the fall of empire is one thing.
However, I wish we could expedite the fall of arrogant ignorance.
This person says you're a Republican now in response to this.
What a lot of you all won't admit is that you are not ready to admit that Israel and
Democrats are not out for your best interests because they have represented good white people
to you.
And that was actually a PSYOP.
They were never good whites.
But then they're co-signed.
Right.
Like how you defending the people, but now got a problem with Dems now.
She don't know what she want, but want people to follow her.
I don't follow people that flip on their original beliefs when they need a better life for themselves.
This arrogant ignorance is a hallmark of being from the United States.
This completely nonsense thought process.
This conflation of learning more information, thus drawing new conclusions as flipping on
original beliefs.
I don't believe in the Republicans and I don't believe in Democrats.
I don't believe in the United States government.
However, we here in the United States have been the subject of a continual psychological operation
of actual untruths, disinformation, manipulation.
When you decolonize from those efforts and begin to learn the truth.
If your original opinions do not change, then you have simply become the latest in their
colonization project.
Two of them right here.
Can't bring everyone with you.
The United States has an unbreakable bond with Israel.
Israel is a true friend.
It is our greatest ally in the region.
The International Criminal Court singles out Israel, but not Iran.
It's great to be here at the annual conference in support of the U.S.-Israel relationship.
A relationship that, of course, is anchored in our shared values.
Always also made clear that we continue to support Israel's right to defend itself.
Let's pray together.